voxpop.com 2011-12-25

# VoxPop

Voxpop.tv  
**Privacy  Policy**

**Last updated on:  February 5, 2011**  
**Consumer Privacy at Voxpop.tv, operated by Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc., an IAC Company**

Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc. (Mindspark) is part of the IAC family of businesses. IAC is an interactive conglomerate with more than 60 brands, including Ask.com, Citysearch, Zwinky, Webfetti, Vimeo.com, Girlsense.com, College Humor, Match.com, and many others. For a list of all of IAC?s businesses, please visit [www.iac.com](http://www.iac.com/ "http://www.iac.com/").  

At Mindspark, we respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they entrust to us. We provide below the basic information policies and practices in place at the Voxpop.tv website.  

**  Information we may collect                                                               **  
We may collect information that can identify you (?personal information?), such as your name and email address, (i) when you provide it to us when using our website or in some other manner, or (ii) from other IAC businesses, from our business partners, and from other third parties.  We may combine the personal information that we receive from different sources. 

We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you visit our website:

  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users? movements around our site and understand trends. 

  * We may assign your computer one or more [cookies](http://www.mindspark.com/main/about/privacy-policy.shtml#cookies) which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience. 

  * We may use standard Internet tools, such [web beacons](http://www.mindspark.com/main/about/privacy-policy.shtml#beacons), which collect information that tracks your use of our website and enables us to customize our services and advertisements. 

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Should we ever do so, we will comply with the Children?s Online Privacy Protection Act.

**Information others may collect                                                         **  
We may allow third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements or place ad tags on our websites. 

  * We do not provide any personal information to these companies. 

  * These companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect information about computers used to view or interact with their advertisements. 

  * Some of these companies may be members of the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), which offers consumers the ability to opt out of ad targeting by all member companies. 

**How we may use information we collect**   
We may use information to:

  * Offer products and services that may be of interest to you; 
  * Customize the advertising and/or content that you see on our websites; 
  * Facilitate use of our websites; 
  * Analyze use of and improve our websites, products and services; 
  * Identify and protect against misuses of our websites; and 
  * Enforce terms of service or other terms/policies governing your use of the Voxpop.tv website. 

**With whom we may share information we collect         **

****  
We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with:

  * Service providers performing services on our behalf; 
  * Other IAC businesses; 
  * Other businesses with which we partner or which we carefully select to offer you products, services, and promotions through our website or offline; and 
  * Other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our users. 

We may share aggregated, non-personal information in any of the above situations and also with advertisers and others. 

**Your choices                                                                                                        **  
You may choose:

  * Not to provide personal information, although that may result in your inability to obtain certain services or use certain features of our websites, products and/or software;
  * To stop receiving promotional emails or newsletters from us by sending an email to the contact address at the bottom of this policy;
  * To delete or decline [cookies](http://www.mindspark.com/main/about/privacy-policy.shtml#cookies) by changing your browser settings, although if you do so, some of the features or services of our website or other products or software may not function properly;

**Security                                                                                                                 **  
We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an email to the email address you most recently provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website.

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions about this summary, our Privacy Policy or our information practices, please contact us by email or postal mail below:

Privacy Officer ? Legal Dept.  
Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc.  
One North Lexington Ave. , 9th Floor  
White Plains, NY, 10601  
Email: privacy[at]mindspark.com  
© 2011 Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc. All rights reserved. 

**GLOSSARY:**

_Cookies_

:  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user?s computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. If accounts are offered, when you sign into your account, we may record your user or member ID and the name on your user or member account in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, we will encrypt any usernames, passwords, and other user or member account-related data that we store in such cookies. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our website to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising.

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click ?Help? in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.

We may allow third-parties, including IAC companies, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party?s privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

_Web Beacons_

: 

Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user?s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may include web beacons in promotional [ _or other_ ] e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website
